{
    "Podstawowa Arytmetyka": [
        {"question": "Ile to 7 + 3?", "answer": 10},
        {"question": "Ile to 15 - 8?", "answer": 7},
        {"question": "Ile to 6 * 4?", "answer": 24},
        {"question": "Ile to 20 / 5?", "answer": 4},
        {"question": "Ile to 9 + 12?", "answer": 21},
        {"question": "Ile to 25 - 10?", "answer": 15},
        {"question": "Ile to 7 * 7?", "answer": 49},
        {"question": "Ile to 36 / 6?", "answer": 6}
    ],
    "Ułamki": [
        {"question": "Ile to 1/2 + 1/4?", "answer": "3/4"},
        {"question": "Ile to 3/4 - 1/2?", "answer": "1/4"},
        {"question": "Ile to 2/3 * 1/2?", "answer": "1/3"},
        {"question": "Ile to 1/5 + 2/5?", "answer": "3/5"},
        {"question": "Ile to 5/6 - 1/3?", "answer": "1/2"}
    ],
    "Potęgi": [
        {"question": "Ile to 2 do potęgi 3 (2^3)?", "answer": 8},
        {"question": "Ile to 5 do potęgi 2 (5^2)?", "answer": 25},
        {"question": "Ile to 10 do potęgi 0 (10^0)?", "answer": 1},
        {"question": "Ile to 3 do potęgi 3 (3^3)?", "answer": 27},
        {"question": "Ile to 4 do potęgi 2 (4^2)?", "answer": 16}
    ]
}